{
	"test": [
		{
			"number": 1,
			"question": "Which fundamental principle of democracy do these excerpts from the US constitution reflect?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_1_1",
			"answers": [
				"Federalism",
				"Limited Government",
				"Separation of Powers",
				"Judicial Review"
			],
			"answer": "Separation of Powers"
		},
		{
			"number": 2,
			"question": "Based on this data, which of the following statements is true?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_1_2",
			"answers": [
				"In 2010, Hispanics were the largest non-white population group.",
				"In 2010, whites accounted for less than half of the US population.",
				"In 2010, blacks were the smallest population group in the US.",
				"In 2010, Asians were the largest non-white population group."
			],
			"answer": "In 2010, Hispanics were the largest non-white population group."
		},
		{
			"number": 3,
			"question": "In the excerpt from the Declaration of Independance, what does the term 'abolish' mean?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_1_3",
			"answers": ["validate", "change", "eliminate", "ignore"],
			"answer": "eliminate"
		},
		{
			"number": 4,
			"question": "Which statement about the popular vote in the 2016 presidential election is supported by the data in the table?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_1_4",
			"answers": [
				"Donald Trump received a majority of the popular vote.",
				"Hilary Clinton received a majority of the popular vote.",
				"No candidate received a majority of the popular vote.",
				"Donald Trump would have received a majority of the popular vote if he had received all of Johnson's support."
			],
			"answer": "No candidate received a majority of the popular vote."
		},
		{
			"number": 5,
			"question": "Consider the following statements:\n\nWhen prices rise, supply increases. When prices fall, supply decreases. \nWhen prices increase, demand falls. \nWhen prices fall, demand increases.\n\nWhich of the following is true?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": [
				"Farmers will produce additional beans when the price per ton goes down by $10.",
				"Manufacturers will produce more tires when the price per tire goes up by $8.",
				"Consumers will buy more apples when the price per dozen goes up by $1.50.",
				"Consumers will buy less ice cream when the price per carton goes down by $1."
			],
			"answer": "Manufacturers will produce more tires when the price per tire goes up by $8."
		},
		{
			"number": 6,
			"question": "What conclusion is supported by the information in the timeline?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_1_5",
			"answers": [
				"The 22nd Amendment was a response to FDR's unprecedented four terms in office.",
				"The attack on Pearl Harbor helped FDR win a third term in office.",
				"FDR failed to fulfill a campaign promise to repeal Prohibition.",
				"Voters elected FDR to a fourth term in order to show their appreciation for victory in WWII."
			],
			"answer": "The 22nd Amendment was a response to FDR's unprecedented four terms in office."
		},
		{
			"number": 7,
			"question": "Three of the following statements about the Korean War are based on facts and evidence. Which one is based on speculation or opinion?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": [
				"More than 34,000 American soldiers died during the Korean War.",
				"The Korean War was the first time jet fighters faced each other in combat.",
				"The United States may have won the Korean War if General Douglas MacArthur had been permitted to use nuclear weapons against Communist forces.",
				"The Korean War began in 1950 and ended with an armistice in 1953."
			],
			"answer": "The United States may have won the Korean War if General Douglas MacArthur had been permitted to use nuclear weapons against Communist forces."
		},
		{
			"number": 8,
			"question": "Which branch of government approves new judges to serve on the Supreme Court?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_1_6",
			"answers": [
				"The Judicial Branch",
				"The Legislative Branch",
				"The Executive Branch",
				"The Voters"
			],
			"answer": "The Legislative Branch"
		},
		{
			"number": 9,
			"question": "The chart best illustrates which of the following principles?",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_1_6",
			"answers": [
				"Federalism",
				"Popular Sovereignty",
				"Judicial Review",
				"Checks and Balances"
			],
			"answer": "Checks and Balances"
		},
		{
			"number": 10,
			"question": "This World War II poster served what function:",
			"graphic": "Social_Quiz_1_7",
			"answers": [
				"Encourage protest against the war.",
				"Promote support for the war.",
				"Encourage the Axis powers to end the war.",
				"Demonstrate the ineffectiveness of guns."
			],
			"answer": "Promote support for the war."
		}
	]
}
